emobucket.com 2018-01-15

# Privacy Policy - Emo Bucket

### Privacy Policy Statement

**The Short Version:** Emo Bucket respects your privacy. We only collect information that is needed such as your username and password, and we do set a cookie (the thing that makes it possible for your browser to remember your login here, and to allow you to actually login). We don't sell your email. You can give us your email and not worry about us selling it, we don't do that. If you need more reassuarance, our full privacy policy is below...

**Emo Bucket**.com Privacy Policy

Our postal address is   
**2201 Lockwood Dr  
Carrollton, Texas 75007**

We can be reached via e-mail at [support@emobucket.com](mailto:support@emobucket.com)  
or you can reach us by telephone at 469-682-2401

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.

We collect information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

The information we collect is used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor and .

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site .

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address.

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:  
http://www.google.com/privacy.html http://www.exponential.com/who-we-are/privacy-policy.jsp

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to the site.

Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.

{CREDITS}
